<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="connection_problem">Connection problem</string>
    <string name="something_went_wrong">Something went wrong</string>
    <string name="we_are_sorry_we_encountered_a_problem">We’re sorry, we encountered a problem while connecting to Flexa. You can submit a report to help us fix the problem, or simply try again later.</string>
    <string name="client_error">Client error</string>
    <string name="send_email">Send email</string>
    <string name="report_email_message_body">Thank you for taking the time to submit this report to Flexa. We’re sorry that this problem happened, and we really appreciate your help.\n\nPlease describe, with as much detail as possible, what you were doing before you ran into this problem:\n\n\n\n————————————————————\nPlease do not edit or delete these details, which will help us with our investigation:</string>
    <string name="flexa_report_email">help@flexa.network</string>
    <string name="report_an_issue">Report an issue</string>

    <string name="flexa">Flexa</string>
    <string name="just_now">Just now</string>
    <string name="to">To</string>
    <string name="invitation_title">%1$s invites you to</string>
    <string name="login_title_1">Spend how you want</string>
    <string name="login_title_2">Designed for privacy</string>
    <string name="login_description_1">Instantly spend your %1$s balances anywhere Flexa is accepted.</string>
    <string name="login_description_2">Flexa was built from the ground up to keep your personal data private.</string>
    <string name="email_description">Flexa uses your email address to sign you in and send you receipts for your payments. Your email address is never shared with %1$s or any other business.</string>
    <string name="about_flexa_and_privacy">About Flexa &amp; Privacy</string>
    <string name="pay_with_flexa">Pay With Flexa</string>
    <string name="whats_your_email_address">What\'s your email address?</string>
    <string name="create_your_flexa_account">Create your Flexa account</string>
    <string name="verify_your_email_address">Verify your email address</string>
    <string name="didnt_get_a_code">Didn\’t get a code?</string>
    <string name="secret_code_description">The 6-digit verification code is displayed after you approve the sign-in request that was sent to your email address. If you don’t remember seeing a code, try opening your verification email again on this device.</string>
    <string name="create_id_description_1">Please provide a few details to start making payments with Flexa.</string>
    <string name="verify_email_description">Just one more step. Check your inbox and tap the link we sent you to verify your email address.</string>
    <string name="create_id_info_description">The information you provide is used only to comply with local financial regulations, and will never be shared with %1$s or any of the businesses you pay. By creating an account, you agree to Flexa’s </string>
    <string name="create_a_flexa_id">Create a Flexa ID</string>
    <string name="sign_in_to_flexa">Sign in to Flexa</string>
    <string name="sign_in_description">Enter the email address associated with your Flexa ID to continue:</string>
    <string name="term_of_use">Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="term_of_service">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="term_of_use_description_compose">By continuing, you confirm that these details are correct and agree to Flexa’s</string>
    <string name="continue_">Continue</string>
    <string name="create_a_flexa_id_description">Enter the details below to create your Flexa ID for spending:</string>
    <string name="first_name">First Name</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="last_name">Last Name</string>
    <string name="email_address">Email Address</string>
    <string name="processing">Processing</string>
    <string name="date_of_birth">Date of Birth</string>
    <string name="creating">Creating</string>
    <string name="please_wait">Please Wait</string>
    <string name="residence">Residence</string>
    <string name="residence_note">Enter the state, province, or territory of your current legal residence.</string>
    <string name="required">Required</string>
    <string name="enter_your_verification_code">Enter your\nverification code</string>
    <string name="secret_code_full_description_1">To finish creating your Flexa ID, click the link we just sent to</string>
    <string name="secret_code_full_description_2">, or enter your secret code below:</string>
    <string name="secret_code_short_description">To finish connecting your Flexa ID, click the link we just sent to </string>
    <string name="open_mail">Open \"Mail\"</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="coppa_title">You must be 13 years of age or older to use Flexa.</string>
    <string name="coppa_description">To protect your privacy, any data you previously provided has been permanently deleted.</string>
    <string name="hawaii_title">An important note for our Hawaii customers</string>
    <string name="hawaii_info">Flexa Network Inc. (“Flexa”) is providing services to you as a participant in a special Hawaii project which ends on December 31, 2022. At the end of the project term, Flexa may be required to close all accounts for Hawaii customers and cease operations. Flexa will notify Hawaii customers in advance if accounts must be closed.\n\nHawaii customers who choose to open accounts with Flexa are advised that the virtual currency or digital currency purchased, whether as an investment, for making payments, or other purposes, may lose value, including the loss of some or all of your original purchase amount.</string>
    <string name="got_it">Got it</string>
    <public type="string" name="logout_description" />
    <string name="logout_description">Are you sure you want to disconnect your Flexa ID?</string>
    <string name="get_started">Get Started</string>
    <string name="report">Report</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="restricted_region_title">Pay with Flexa is not available in your region.</string>
    <string name="restricted_region_copy">Federal law prevents Flexa from making its services available in some regions. For more information, please contact Flexa support.</string>
</resources>
